

EDOARDO VINCENZI

WEB DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

I'm an ambitious and driven individual. I like challenges. I'm always looking for opportunity to do better and grow. I'm humble and i want learn new skills for improve myself.

I worked in two companies, for about three years overall, where i learned how to work in a team, how to organize my tasks and how to manage problems.

LANGUAGES

English: B1 Certificate Italian: Native

CONTACTS

Telephone number: +39 3402136572

Website: www.edoardovincenzi.it

Email: edoardo.vincenzi95@gmail.com

Linkedin: @edoardo-vincenzi

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web developer

Enerj srl (01/2021 - 09/2021)

- Analyse software specifications
- Implement front-end website design
- Computer programming
- Develop and Software maintenance
- Debug software
- Web programming
- Use software libraries
- Style sheet languages
- .NET
- JavaScript
- HTMI
- Razor HTML
- Postgres SQL

ICT system developer

Archiva Srl (06/2017 - 03/2019)

- Design, develop and distribute applications for mission-critical systems
- Software: Informatica Data Transformation Studio
- Software: Altova MapForce for mapping source system data (xml files, flat files, csv, edifact) to data warehouse tables
- Knowledge basic of SQL Server, Oracle, DB2, MariaDB for SQL programming

EDUCATION

University of Verona

Bachelor's degree Computer Science (10/2014 - 12/2020)

First / second year Basic mathematical and physical skills Basic computer skills:

- Programming and algorithms
- Computer architectures, operating systems and computer networks

Second / third year Additional specific skills:

- Databases and information systems
- Fundamentals of information technology
- Programming languages
- Compilers
- Advanced programming techniques
- Computer graphics

Industrial Informatics (ABACUS)

High school Computer Science (2009 - 2014)

INTERESTS AND HOBBY

I love reading fantasy and personal growth books. i love going to gym.

I love studying a new technology and programming.